<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts! on Kyle's homepage</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts! on Kyle's homepage</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Platform bed</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2015-10-31-platform-bed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2015-10-31-platform-bed/</guid><description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back in February, my wife Rachel and I started work on a new set of bedroom furniture.
It began with little things like a headboard&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and a bookcase&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The largest project so far is a bed. I took a lot of time cobbling together
various tutorials and images from across the web and Seattle&amp;rsquo;s many furniture stores to
finally settle on a platform bed that looks a lot like Crate and Barrel&amp;rsquo;s
&lt;a href="http://www.crateandbarrel.com/furniture/beds/atwood-bed-with-bookcase/f42064"&gt;Atwood&lt;/a&gt; bed.
It turned out pretty simple and feels solid several months later, so here are the plans!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CardDav with Fastmail</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2014-12-28-fastmail-carddav/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2014-12-28-fastmail-carddav/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;So you heard about Fastmail&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="http://blog.fastmail.com/2014/12/22/carddav-beta-release/"&gt;CardDav beta&lt;/a&gt;?
Finding their &lt;a href="https://beta.fastmail.com/help/clients/applist.html"&gt;setup page&lt;/a&gt; lacking?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So did I!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking a look at their &lt;a href="https://www.fastmail.com/help/technical/servernamesandports.html?domain=fastmail.fm"&gt;servers and ports page&lt;/a&gt;
(at the time of this writing) gave me the clues I needed. Try these settings with the &amp;ldquo;CardDav-sync beta&amp;rdquo; app:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;</description></item><item><title>Some Vim Window, Tab, and Buffer Commands</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2013-03-07-some-vim-window-tab-and-buffer-commands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2013-03-07-some-vim-window-tab-and-buffer-commands/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is mostly a short record for myself, but here go the basic Vim window,
buffer and tab commands I like to use/know. My encouragement to learn effective
use of all three stems from &lt;a href="http://blog.sanctum.geek.nz/buffers-windows-tabs/"&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;
nice post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="windows"&gt;Windows&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Windows are for viewing things side by side. I only recently started getting to
know these, but they&amp;rsquo;re super useful and make you look like a total badass.
To create a new window you &amp;ldquo;split&amp;rdquo; your current one using the commands&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Interview Ready</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-12-30-interview-ready/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-12-30-interview-ready/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a job! Well, really I want to find an awesome next
step in my career as a software engineer. It&amp;rsquo;s a tough battle to
track down the places I want to work, get application materials
ready, get applications in in the right order (NP-Hard without a
doubt), be prompt with my emails, and prepare for those interviews.
I figure it might be nice to put down some resources and things I
wish I had known.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Organizing Dotfiles</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-10-30-organizing-dotfiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-10-30-organizing-dotfiles/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I did it! My dotfiles are pretty well organized now, and I love it. I recently
swapped out my os only to discover my terminal configuration is now painless.
After installing Git, I just have to clone and then copy things to the correct
places.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, you either know what a dotfile is and want to back up
yours with ease, or you have no idea what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. Let&amp;rsquo;s deal with
the latter first, then return to what I did with my files.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Launching LendingShack</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-09-10-launching-lendingshack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-09-10-launching-lendingshack/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Whew! (You can find &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rdquo; &lt;a href="http://lendingshack.com"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for those impatient enough to
not read on.) Joey and I did it. We launched an actual website. After getting on
with the CentsLess team, we worked all summer to break in our actual coding
chops, learn Django, learn the Internets, and build a working product. It was
an incredible challenge, filled with discouraging and elating moments in droves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I never imagined taking on such a massive project so early, but Joey and I
inspired one another to tackle this together. For us, it was a huge leap to
produce something like this. We learned about Django, Heroku, Amazon S3,
and more HTML/CSS3/Javascript than we ever imagined knowing. I hope to share
some of the lessons in technical posts over the coming weeks (time permitting).
Getting through these technical challenges is something no class experience can
teach, and I&amp;rsquo;m really glad I had a partner to work through it with.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sitting down after standing up</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-09-10-sitting-down-after-standing-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-09-10-sitting-down-after-standing-up/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I had no idea what to write about my experience standing up at work, until I got
back to school and had to sit down again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Standing was definitely the best thing I could do at work and in general. I
felt in better shape, more alert, and generally happier about my day. It
might sound silly, but sitting down is exhausting. To skip the boring details,
let&amp;rsquo;s just say my back pain went away after starting to stand.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Standing up in my cube</title><link>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-07-17-standing-up-in-my-cube/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.krwenholz.com/posts/2012-07-17-standing-up-in-my-cube/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I know it&amp;rsquo;s a fad by now, but I just switched over to a stand-up desk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After getting into the groove of things, my job had me sitting down most of
the time. It only took about two weeks of this for my back to begin hurting
and my posture to crumble into chaos. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stand it! So I stood up ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some research, including a few prompts from &lt;a href="http://lifehacker.com"&gt;Lifehacker&lt;/a&gt;,
led me to consider the idea of a standing desk. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to commit to
one of the incredibly expensive, but very nice, desks you find through
conventional shopping means. Not to be deterred, the cheap and effective
solution eventually came across my screen: &lt;a href="http://iamnotaprogrammer.com/Ikea-Standing-desk-for-22-dollars.html"&gt;Ikea&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>